

## PROFILE & CONTACT

9 Name : Dhaker SALAH

Date of birth: 15/06/1996

**Q** Location: Monastir, Tunisia

Phone: +21655635707

Email: dhakersalah15@gmail.com

Github: github.com/DhakerSalah

inkedIn: linkedin.com/in/dhakersalah

## **SOFTWARES**

Office, Adobe Photoshop, VScode, StarUml, Xampp, Postman, Putty, WinSCP, Git, Gitlab, Github, Twilio, Trello, Slack.

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Front End**

HTML

CSS

**BOOTSTRAP** 

JAVASCRIPT

. - - - - - - -

JQUERY ANGULAR

REACT JS

## **Back End**

DJANGO FLASK

LARAVEL

**Databases** 

MYSQL

**MONGO DB** 

**PostgreSQL** 

**Modelization** 

**UML** 

**Mobile** 

**REACT NATIVE** 

# **DHAKER SALAH**

## Software engineer

# **ABOUT ME**

Achieving the career of your dreams is not impossible when you know where to start...

As a certified scrum web developer participated in and developed a wide range of projects, I am a computer engineer specializing in software engineering.

My training is proof of my autonomy and my adaptability, and my professional experiences have allowed me to develop my critical sense.

On the personal side, I am a rather communicative, sociable, attentive and reliable person. I have an active life position and I am driven by a strong curiosity to learn, hardworking, rigorous, available and I have a good sense of direction.

#### **FORMATION**

2019/2022 Monastir/Tunisia **National Engineering Diploma in Software Engineering** 

Private polytechnic school of Monastir

2016/2019 Sousse/Tunisia Fundamental license in computer management computing

Higher Institute of Management of Sousse

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Jobs** 

SBG TECHELECTRO: Web Developer (Python, JavaScript)

(Jul 2023 - Today)

- Analyse of needs.
- Design and implement models and services for an existing project.
- Convert a non-relational database (NoSQL) to a relational database (SQL) by migrating data and changing functions according to the new architecture.
- Work with Google Cloud Storage (GCS).
- Deploy a project in Azure and a database on the DigitalOcean.
- Software versioning (Git).
- Test the endpoints after the database migration and the backend part of the project.

**Carnelian Digital Innovation:** Django Backend Developer

(Oct 2022 - May 2023)

- Analyse of needs.
- Recommend and implement technical solutions according to deadlines, budget and human resources.
- Test in an acceptance environment and validate with the whole team the functionalities put in place.
- Work with Celery, Redis and Elasticsearch.
- Security and access management.
- Database administration (PostgreSQL).
- Software versioning (Git).
- Evolution in an agile environment (scrum).

Internships

#### CLEVERTECH FRANCE (07 Feb 2022 - 08 Jul 2022)

- Development of a web & mobile application for restaurant management (DJANGO – REACT JS – REACT NATIVE – AGILE SCRUM – AZURE).
- Generate QR codes.
- Integrate the Twilio and the SendGrid tools.

GROUPE FLORUS (01 Aug 2021 - 31 Aug 2021)

 Development of a web application for users management (ANGULAR – SPRING BOOT – AGILE SCRUM).

CARTHAGE SOLUTION (10 Aug 2020 - 10 Sep 2020)

• Development of a web application for company management

### **MASTERING**

- ✓ Attention to details
- ✓ Ability to anticipate
- ✓ Team spirit
- ✓ Remote work
- ✓ Excellent analytical skills
- ✓ Sense of organization

# **INTERESTS**

- ✓ Chess.
- ✓ Swimming.
- ✓ Football.
- ✓ Photography.

## **LANGUAGES**

✓ Arabic : Native language✓ Frensh : Good level

English : Medium



(HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, MYSQL).

Create a client project with WordPress.

**DEV-GX** (11 Feb 2019 - 10 May 2019)

• Design and development of a web application of human resources management (ANGULAR – LARAVEL).

SANCELLA (01 Jul 2018 - 31 Jul 2018)

Development of a leave web application in PHP.

**Events** 

#### **DIGITAL MARKETING 2017/2018**

At Higher Institute of Management of Sousse

#### **COMPUTER NIGHT: 2019/2020 & 2020/2021**

International event

Certificates

Coursera - Meta

(Meta Backend Developer)

https://coursera.org/verify/professional-cert/BB6YY4TNTBRC

SCRUM study

(Scrum Fundamentals Certified)

https://www.scrumstudy.com/certification/verify?type=SFC&number=891020

LinkedIn Learning

(Become a Software Developer)

https://www.linkedin.com/learning/certificates/0feaea34dd19fff06127deb79 0b471769a0d68b5e13e137116237ff5fc853f6f

**➢** IBM

(IBM Academic Certificate exam for Big Data Engineer)

Microsoft

(HTML MTA - CSS MTA - JavaScript MTA – Database administration MTA – Software development MTA)

OpenClassrooms

(Administer your databases with MySQL)
(Design your website with PHP and MySQL)
(Learn how to create your website with HTML5 and CSS3)
(Learn to code with JavaScript)

Udacity

(Full Stack Development Track)

Saylor Academy

(CS305 : Web Development)

Own projects

- ❖ Shopping website (PHP).
- Hotel booking website (PHP).
- \* Reservation in restaurant (PHP).
- Restaurant management platform (PHP).
- \* RH management (PHP & Angular-Laravel).
- Bank account management application (Spring boot).

Freelance

Solar energy management platform (PHP).